Episode 9            A Person To Love
Senpai is popular at college...
A classmate of mine
asked me out at college today.
Are you gonna get homewrecked?
Nooo!
No way! No way!
I'm pretty sure you don't need to worry.
This is an end-of-the-universe level disaster...
That is some sense of scale.
It's because Senpai's cool!
And... he's fun to be around,
and in spite of how he seems,
you can always rely on him in a pinch!
And then there's the fact...
I like Onii-chan too.
To be honest, I do too.
Wha?!
This stupid world...
I'll destroy this stupid world!
Disproportionate!
How are things in drama lately?
We've got a promising new rookie.
What's he like?
It's a girl.
Huh, wish I could meet her.
Oh... right... sure...
How are things at college, Senpai?
Me?
Well, my drama club didn't meet,
so it was pretty uneventful.
Anything else?
I'd like to hear more...
about how college is going.
Why? You worried about something?!
Oh, no, not at all!
If nothing's going on,
that's good to know, too.
If you say so, but let me know
if anything comes up, okay?
I wanna be there to help you.
He has to be popular!
That made me happy...
But it'll make him popular!
H-Honestly... I've been really wondering
if you're popular at college...
Me?!
What the heck made you think that?
That girl asked you out...
That was just... I mean,
I sure don't feel popular.
Besides, it's not like I have time
to think about other girls.
You're bound to be popular!
But why?!
Senpai... are you doing anything tomorrow?
Oh, tomorrow is the anniversary
of the high school's founding, right?
Gotta love a day off.
I'd like to see you
when you're done with class...
But I've got club tomorrow...
How about you come by the campus, Rin?
Oh, well... I'd love to,
but... is that allowed?
If someone says something,
we'll just say you've come for a tour.
You can even sneak into a class!
Now I can actually check
and see how popular he is!
But it's kind of scary...
But I get to see Senpai first thing
in the morning tomorrow!
What should I wear?!
You're as expressive as you've always been.
You realize I can see you, right?
And now the screen's blacked out!
The camera's malfunctioning... that's it.
I've successfully snuck in!
Just gotta keep a low profile.
If I signal you like this,
then you need to hide.
Right!
I'm attending the same class as Senpai...
It's like a dream.
Wait, no! I need to observe him today!
A sporty girl!
I bet she'd get along with Senpai,
with how energetic they are...
Like some sort of Cheerful-chan!
She's gorgeous!
And she's got sexy body language...
A Classy-chan!
What are you doing, Senpai?
Isn't that the signal to hide?
Guess who?
Imp-chan after our gazes have met
for the third time during class.
Gimme another quiz!
Rin, who is always
using her acting
to help people
have a good time!
Rin, who is always using her acting
to help people have a good time!
This'd be embarrassing
to say out loud, but...
Thanks for everything.
I'd...
like to hear it from you directly, though.
Not "Eh?"
Come on!
Oh, there you are, Kitahama-kun.
Good morning.
Care to join us for lunch today?
No way... it's that
pretty lady from earlier!
Huh?
Is this the kouhai I've heard so much about?
This is her. She came in secret.
Rin, these gals are from my acting club.
It's nice to meet you...
Hey there!
Does that mean you spend
a lot of time together?
Well... yeah.
They're all girls...
Only relatively! Subjectively! In contrast!
I get the feeling we'd be
interrupting something.
Sorry about that...
Excuse me!
I'd like to eat lunch with you!
Rin... You sure?
We're not gonna get
a lot of chances like today.
You two will have less time together.
I came here to see how
popular Senpai is at college!
I won't get many other chances!
Huh. You mean with us?
I'll jump straight to the point.
Kitahama-kun's not particularly popular.
Really?
I mean,
usually he just makes a bunch of noise
with Iwata-kun and the other guy.
J-Just making noise?!
Exactly like that.
The other day, you got into an fight
over the last pudding at the school store...
Got the last one!
Give her back to me!
Pudding
You can take her...
Personally, I'm not into... exuberant guys.
See what I mean, Rin?
I'm not popular at all.
Also, aren't they mean?
Senpai...
I'm... kind of relieved.
You basically just finished me off...
now I'm actually kinda bummed.
Maybe I should start crying and fussing!
He's at it again...
You can have this, so please cheer up!
Everything about the previous
engagement was so wonderful.
Miss Elizabeth's piano was quite something.
Her cooking was incredible, as well.
You really think so?
Truly, the venison rounds
were prepared just right.
Oh, truly?
I'd love to hear you play our piano
someday. It's simply exquisite.
Everyone was discussing how they'd never
seen such splendid cuts of meat before.
Even Mr. Darcy thought so...
Most likely more than yours...
Good evening, Mrs. Catherine.
Begging your pardon, but I need
to have a word with Miss Elizabeth...
In private.
Whatever about?
Elizabeth.
There's something...
that I feel I must tell you.
Yes?
I have always been...
a rather high-handed man,
of hard-to-tolerate character.
Meeting you has made me
more aware of that fact.
I'd like to apologize...
Well, I should also apologize
for misunderstanding you.
And I'd like to offer thanks
on behalf of my entire family
for how kindly you've treated Lydia.
It's been a while since I've seen it,
but Nanakura-san is still an amazing actress.
And this is with no preparation!
Who is that?
Even the older members are all captivated.
She's in high school still...
I was the one who invited her to drama club!
I'm kind of a big deal to her.
Why you little...
You just don't get it, do you?
Listen up...
You're a cocky, dense goober.
I believe I know you very well.
If you had no intention of getting married,
you would've told Mrs. Catherine as much.
And she's a hard-working actress who knows
how to go with the flow.
That's true!
You know just how much
I won't mince words about how I feel.
Considering how, when
I refused your previous proposal,
I insulted you so harshly...
But...
Who do you think is the real prize?
I honestly feel ashamed
of how I had acted before...
Mr. Darcy... if you still feel
the same way...
Elizabeth... would you...
take me as your husband?
Which one do you think
people take seriously?
Yes... gladly.
Pseudo Harem
If you still feel the same way...!
Then... will you marry me?
Yes, gladly!
Hold it right there!
S-Senpai?
Talk about a bad ending!
Good luck, buddy.
Hey, you there! What are you doing?!
Eiji!
Senpai!
Hey! We don't need any props in here!
Come by again some time!
Seeya!
Senpai, why'd you rush the scene like that?
Well...
I think I understand where you
were coming from before.
And maybe I was worried...
But the way you were acting was too much!
It's just what the script says...
I wanna clobber whoever picked
that script with a hammer!
Well, what did you think of my performance?
It was... really good.
Which is probably what
made me even more worried...
I guess we both ended up
worrying about the same thing.
You said you weren't
worried anymore, though...
Just a bit! It's not like
I can totally rest easy.
So we're in the same boat.
Or maybe you'd rest easier
if we got married?
P-Please say something...
Now I'm worried about
something else altogether!
The ceremony?! And honeymoon?!
Where do we live?! How many kids?!
Are they gonna cry all night?!
Rebellious phases?!
Senpai! That was just acting! Acting!
Their coming of age ceremonies?!
Their marriages?!
"The rain's making everything glitter!
The birdies are in a great mood,
and even the rainbow is crobbing..."
That was cute, how you flubbed that.
But I flubbed it!
Guess you're glad it
wasn't in front of Senpai-san, huh?
"Tonight, my parents are glowing bout..."
...I need to rehearse more.
So serious!
Although I happen to like it
when you slack when acting.
I only slack around you, Megu!
Aw, how's that taste for you, little baby?
Yummy-wummy! It taste weally good!
Seriously, I only do this
sort of thing in front of you!
Now show me how Baby-chan would eat!
You realize I'm a high
school senior, right?!
I want you to try that for Senpai-san!
I bet he'd think it was cute!
You only get this because
we're childhood friends!
You should probably be grateful!
Fank yoo berry much!
Megu...
Do you wanna go somewhere
on our next day off?
You sure? Not gonna see Senpai-san?
But I barely hang out with you anymore.
You've grown into such a sweet girl...
I'd love some steak.
What're you saying?!
I've been so lonely... please be nice to me!
Wehhh, baby no understand!
Treat me, Baby-chan!
Senpai!
Nanakura-senpai, um,
can I talk to you for a moment?
Kiri-chan...
Go ahead.
Uh... so what is it?
I was... hoping you'd
read some lines with me.
Oh, okay, sure thing.
"I can't believe we're siblings, now..."
"I don't like it either."
"You had better not tell anyone at school!"
Okay.
I don't think you have anything
to worry about for the next performance.
That was better than
I'd expect from a first-year.
But... I feel like my acting
hasn't been good enough lately.
And it's your fault, Nanakura-senpai!
Um, s-sorry...
No... it's just, when
I first saw your acting...
I... couldn't look away.
Not just on a technical level,
but... how do I put this...
The way you were on stage...
It's okay, take your time.
Please, don't be embarrassed.
Nanakura-senpai...
how are you able to act like that?
I want to get to know you better!
Kiri-chan... is there anyone you like?
When you care about someone,
you start to think more about what's
going on in their head than your own,
day after day...
and you can feel your emotions
changing like you're a different person.
I think that might be what
helps me figure out roles...
Or maybe not!
Then there's someone you
care about, Nanakura-senpai?
Yep!
I... haven't ever really felt
that way before.
You seem pretty dedicated to the club, yeah.
And lately I've been thinking
about you all the time, Nanakura-senpai...
I see...
No, not like that!
That's not what I meant...
the way I like you is more pure...
You like me?!
Wait, no!
I mean, it's true, but...
When I say like I mean...
Easy there, Kiri-chan! Let's just calm down!
Make it stop...!
My family is going to visit relatives
in the country over the summer.
But I'm going to be staying
behind to watch the house!
Rin... you don't have to act cheery...
If you're lonely, it's okay to cry, y'know?
Oh, no, it's not that!
What I mean is that, once it's summer break...
Would you come over to my place?
Say what?!
Looks like this is gonna
be one hell of a hot summer!
Wait, what?
Much Ado About Nothing!
I've got my lovely wife...
And we're surrounded by our plucky kids!
Is that us?!
I'm so happy...
I feel like, from a performance standpoint,
I could express this bliss better
if I had my head in your lap.
And if that's what the role calls for...!
I-In my lap?!